Oliver Tambo Papers 2000.0144
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series B: Office of the President, 1962-1992
  - Office of the Secretary General (Box B8)
      - Correspondence (Box B8., Folder 1.1)
        - Correspondence (Addressed to and generated by the Office of the Secretary General, 31 items), 1975 September - 1990 (Box B8., Folder 1.1.4)
          Correspondents include Afro-Asian Peoples' Solidarity Organisation; French Communist Party; Italian Socialist Party; National Christian Council of Kenya; National Council of Trade Unions ( NACTU/ South Africa); Swedish Social Democratic Party ( Bernt Carlsson); UNESCO; World Congress of Peace Forces; World Peace Council. Correspondence with Fantuzzi, Giolio (Mayor of Reggio Emilia); Madagascar (Minister of Foreign Affairs); Margaret Thatcher; United National Independence Party ( UNIP/ Zambia).
      - Reports (19 items) (Box B8., Folder 1.2)
        - Miscellaneous
          - On the Portuguese Coup d’etat. 4p. Ms.
          - The OAU and the Liberation Struggle. 6p. Ts.
          - Report on Solidarity Work: J Jele, 1973 November 12
          - A Brief Report of the Activities. 38p. Ts., 1917 September - 1974 April
          - Draft Report of the Sub-Committee for the Release of Political Prisoners. 8p. Ts.
      - Speeches/Statements of the Secretary General, Alfred Nzo (11 items), 1968, 1968-1975, 1978 (Box B8., Folder 1.3)
        - 1968 - 1981 (Box B8., Folder 1.3.1)
          - Statement delivered on behalf of the India Office of the ANC to the 71st Session of the Indian Congress, Hyderabad, 3p. Ts., 1968
          - Greetings to the Government and People of the Soviet Union on the occasion of the 52nd Anniversary of the Great October Socialist Revolution, 2p. Ts., 1969
          - Message delivered on the occasion of South Africa n Freedom Day, 1974 June 26 June
          - Hands off Angola, 1975
        - A Statement of the ANC delivered by Alfred Nzo at a Conference of the Continuation Committee of the Lisbon International Conference in Support of the Peoples of Southern Africa, London, 1979 March 21 - 23 (Box B8., Folder 1.3.1)
          - How and why a small ANC clique decided to make a public emergence at this time and state in the development of our situation, 1978
        - 1982-1984 (19 items) (Box B8., Folder 1.3.2)
          - Press Statement by Comrade Alfred Nzo to the Youth of South Africa on the occasion of the 6th Anniversary of the June 16th Soweto Uprising. 3p. Ts.
          - Statement re Week of Solidarity with the Colonial Peoples of Southern Africa. 3p. Ts.
          - Statement to the Canadian Conference in Solidarity with the Liberation Struggles of the Peoples of Southern Africa, Ottawa. 10p. Ts., 1982 May 7 - 9
          - Statement at the Scientific Seminar to mark the centenary of the birth of Georgi Dimitrov, Sofia. 5p. Ts., 1982 June 15 - 17
        - Radio Freedom Broadcast of the Secretary-General to the People of South Africa. 7p. Ts., 1982 June 26 (Box B8., Folder 1.3.2)
          - Statement at the Seminar on Karl Marx. 7p. Ts., 1983 April 11 - 16
          - A Call for Urgent Action. Statement by Secretary General Nzo. 2p., 1984 May 5
        - Undated Speeches/Statements (7 items) (Box B8., Folder 1.3.3)
      - Miscellaneous (10 items), 1982-1990 (Box B8., Folder 1.4)
        Programmes; lists; notices, etc.
    - Department of Arts and Culture (Box B8., Folder 2)
      - Barbara Masekela - Administrative Secretary (Box B8., Folder 2.1)
        - Correspondence
        - 1982-1985 (69 items) (Box B8., Folder 2.1.1)
        - 1986 (22 items) (Box B8., Folder 2.1.2)
        - 1987-1989 (26 items) (Box B8., Folder 2.1.3)
      - General/Departmental (Box B8., Folder 2.2)
        - Correspondence (18 items), 1982-1990 (Box B8., Folder 2.2.2.1)
          Correspondents include Fitzgerald, Patrick (Assistant Secretary for International Cultural Affairs/Administrative Secretary); Khosa, Rufus (Assistant Secretary for Projects); Maluleka, Jubilee Lizwe (Amandla Liaison Officer); Mokwena, Bachana (Amandla Administrator).
        - Reports/Proposals/Position Papers/Memoranda (Box B8., Folder 2.2.2)
          - 1969, 1982-1986 (13 items) (Box B8., Folder 2.2.2.1)
            Items include Report on the 1st Pan African Cultural Festival; Amandla Cultural Ensemble Reports; state of the Department of Arts and Culture.
          - 1987-1988 (12 items) (Box B8., Folder 2.2.2.2)
            Items include proposal for Amandla Cultural Ensemble to live and study in Cuba for one year; CASA - Culture in Another South Africa Reports.
          - 1989 (9 items) (Box B8., Folder 2.2.2.3)
            Items include Cultural Boycott Seminar; ANC In-House Seminar on Culture and Sport; draft paper on Albie Sachs - Preparing ourselves for freedom.
        - Publications (Box B8., Folder 2.2.3)
          - DAC Newsletter, No. 1
          - Culture News, No. 2, (1990)
          - Rixaka: Cultural Journal of the ANC, 1989-1990
        - Other Publications (Box B8., Folder 2.2.4)
          - Information Bulletin - International Conference against Apartheid Sport, 1987 November
          - Alex Arts Centre News, 1986 December
        - Speech/Statements (Box B8., Folder 2.2.5)
          - Draft speech for Cultural Boycott Workshop organised by Irish AAA
          - Statement of the NICC on the Cultural Boycott
          - Joint Communiqué from the ANC/Afrikaans Writers Conference, 1989
        - Miscellaneous (Box B8., Folder 2.2.6)
          - Lists: Members of Amandla Cultural Ensemble/Proposal - conference of journalists
          - Pamphlet: Amandla Zimbabwe Tour, 1988
          - Press Cutting, " ANC leader criticizes Simon on Graceland"
    - Department of Economics (Box B8., Folder 3)
      - Head of Department-- Max Sisulu (Box B8., Folder 3.1)
        - Correspondence (Box B8., Folder 3.1.1)
        - 1987-1990 (12 items)
      - Reports (Box B8., Folder 3.2)
        - undated, 1979-1987 (10 items) (Box B8., Folder 3.2.1)
        - 1988, 1990 (6 items) (Box B8., Folder 3.2.2)
          Proceedings of the ANC In-House Seminar on Social Welfare which took place in Lusaka on 28-30 July 1988; Neither Japan nor South Korea, but a New South Africa. A Critique of Peter Berger: Z. Pallo Jordan; Draft Economic Policy Document; Discussion Document on Economic Policy.
      - Press Statement (1 item), 1990
        Press Statement on the consultative Workshop organised by the ANC's Department of Economics and Planning, COSATU and The Economic Trends Group on the theme: South Africa - Towards a Post-Apartheid Economy.
      - Other Individual/Organisations (Box B8., Folder 3.4)
        - Reports/Speeches (Box B8., Folder 3.4.1)
          - 1981, 1985 (3 items) (Box B8., Folder 3.4.1.1)
          - 1986, 1987 March (2 items) (Box B8., Folder 3.4.1.2)
          - 1987 April -1990 (5 items) (Box B8., Folder 3.4.1.3)
          - Undated (5 items) (Box B8., Folder 3.4.1.4)
      - South African Economic Research and Training Project (SAERT) (Box B8., Folder 3.5)
        - Correspondence (4 items), 1985-1987, 1989 (Box B8., Folder 3.5.1)
        - Policy Workshop (Box B8., Folder 3.5.2)
          - Pamphlet (advertising the workshop)
          - Outline of Sessions and Papers
          - Report of Workshop, 1987 March
        - Reports (Box B8., Folder 3.5.3)
          - SAERT Summary Progress Report, prepared by S. Matlhape and S. Choabi
          - Research and Training for Economic Planning in Post-Apartheid South Africa, 1986 May
          - Memorandum addressed to Oliver Tambo re SAERT (Matlhape Project)
    - Department of Education (Box B8., Folder 4)
      - Secretary for Education-- H. G. Makgothi (Box B8., Folder 4.1)
        - Correspondence (24 items), 1982-1988
      - Secretary for Education-- M. S. Choabi (Box B8., Folder 4.2)
        - Correspondence/Memoranda/Reports (20 items), 1982-1990 (Box B8., Folder 4.2.1)
        - Speeches/Statements (4 items), undated, 1989 (Box B8., Folder 4.2.2)
      - Administrative Secretary-- M. Tikly (Box B8., Folder 4.3)
        - Correspondence (15 items), 1988-1989
    - General (Box B8., Folder 5)
      - Correspondence (8 items), 1977-1990 (Box B8., Folder 5.1)
      - Miscellaneous (3 items) (Box B8., Folder 5.2)
        Includes: correspondence generated by The Southern African Advanced Education Project ( Ann Yates) re: Public Service Training - Induction Programme for High Level Posts; List of Participants: Seminar on Education and Culture for Liberation in Southern Africa; ANC Department of Education - Newsletter (October 1992).
      - Reports/Memoranda (Box B8., Folder 5.3)
        - undated, 1980 - April 1988 + undated items (12 items) (Box B8., Folder 5.3.1)
        - 1988 June - 1990 (7 items) (Box B8., Folder 5.3.2)
      - Education Courses and Scholarships (Box B8., Folder 5.4)
        - Correspondence (32 items), 1968-1989 (Box B8., Folder 5.4.1)
        - Minutes/Reports (2 items), 1986 (Box B8., Folder 5.4.2)
        - Lists: Students applying for Scholarships (7 items), 1968-1969 (Box B8., Folder 5.4.3)
        - Miscellaneous (5 items) (Box B8., Folder 5.4.4)
          Includes application forms; miscellaneous lists of courses and other requirements.
        - Information Booklets, Institutions offering Scholarships (4 items) (Box B8., Folder 5.4.5)
      - 3rd - 5th National Educational Council Meetings (Box B8., Folder 5.5)
        - Reports/Minutes (4 items), 1980-1983
        - 6th National Educational Council Meeting (Box B8., Folder 5.6)
          - Reports in published and unpublished form, 1986
        - 7th National Educational Council Meeting (Box B8., Folder 5.7)
          - Preparatory Memoranda (4 items), 1988
        - Solomon Mahlangu Freedom College ( SOMAFCO) (Box B8., Folder 5.8)
          - M. W. Njobe - Principal (Box B8., Folder 5.8.1)
            - Correspondence (5 items), 1979-1980
          - T. K. Maseko - Principal (Box B8., Folder 5.8.2)
            - Correspondence (4 items), 1982
          - Mohammed Tikly - Director (Box B8., Folder 5.8.3)
            - Correspondence (15 items), 1983-1986
        - General (Box B8., Folder 5.8.4)
          - Correspondence (15 items), 1981-1989 (Box B8., Folder 5.8.4.1)
            Items include citation from the SOMAFCO Nursery School to Oliver Tambo following his visit to the community; request addressed to Oliver Tambo to look after Sasa Zikalala on the part of Fieke Vermeulen and Willem Van Harderwijk (Mazimbu).
          - Reports (Box B8., Folder 5.8.4.2)
            - Proposals on ANC (SA) School Project
            - Memorandum to the Government of Italy concerning cooperation with the exiled community in Dakawa and Mazimbu ( Tanzania) and in other Front Line States through the executing NGO's
            - UN Development Programme - Preparatory Education Assistance to the ANC
            - Reports/Memoranda (13 items), 1978-1982 (Box B8., Folder 5.4.2.1)
              Items include water supply scheme; principal’s interim report; pregnancies amongst students; inquiry into a motor accident involving students at Mazimbu.
            - Reports/Memoranda (17 items), 1983-1990 (Box B8., Folder 5.8.4.2.2)
              Items include School Year Reports; visit to Italy of a SOMAFCO Delegation to Italy; G. V. Reddy’s report on his psychiatric work/observations at Mazimbu/Dakawa; analysis of examination results.
          - Publications (Box B8., Folder 5.8.4.3)
            - Somafco Magazine (3 items) (Box B8., Folder 5.8.4.3.1)
            - Miscellaneous (9 items) (Box B8., Folder 5.8.4.3.2)
              Items include: Speeches/Notices; Programmes; Textbooks/Educational Aids
        - SOMAFCO/DAKAWA (Box B8., Folder 5.8.5)
          - Progress Reports (Box B8., Folder 5.8.5.1)
            - 1982-1983
            - Official opening of SOMAFCO: Progress Report Special Edition (including the ANC Development Centre - Dakawa)
        - Dakawa Vocational Training Centre (Box B8., Folder 5.8.6)
          - M. W. Njobe - Principal (Box B8., Folder 5.8.6.1)
            - Correspondence (10 items), 1985-1989
          - Miscellaneous Correspondence (4 items), 1982, 1988, 1989 (Box B8., Folder 5.8.6.2)
          - Reports (Box B8., Folder 5.8.6.3)
            - 1984 (3 items) (Box B8., Folder 5.8.6.3.1)
              Items include Royal Norwegian Ministry of Foreign Affairs on behalf of ANC (SA): Dakawa Development Centre, Tanzania (Volumes 1-3)
            - Reports (7 items), 1985-1989 (Box B8., Folder 5.8.6.3.2)
            - Miscellaneous (6 items) (Box B8., Folder 5.8.6.3.4)
              Items include Memoranda/Speech/Outline of Vocational Training Programme/Handbook on course outlines.
        - Mazimbu/Dakawa (Box B8., Folder 5.8.7)
          - Mazimbu Works Committee (Box B8., Folder 5.8.7.1)
            - Correspondence (1 item), 1983
          - Bulletins/Publications (Box B8., Folder 5.8.7.2)
            - Works Committee Information Bulletin, No. 22, 31 (10 items), 1983-1984 (Box B8., Folder 5.8.7.2.1)
            - Hlanganani: Mazimbu Workers Monthly Bulletin, No. 32, 41-57 (9 items), 1984-1985 (Box B8., Folder 5.8.7.2.2)
          - Mazimbu/Dakawa News and Views, 1984-1989 (Box B8., Folder 5.8.7.2.3)
    - Department of Health (Box B8., Folder 6)
      - Correspondence (9 items), 1982-1991 (Box B8., Folder 6.1)
        Items include appeal in the case of Phakiso Make; resignations - Pren Naicker/ Regina Nzo.
      - Reports/Papers/Memoranda (5 items), undated, 1969, 1990 (Box B8., Folder 6.2)
        Items include Seminar Report - "Towards comprehensive intervention strategies for the prevention and control of AIDS/HIV infection" (1990); discussion document for ANC branches towards developing a health policy; "Malaria and You" by Regina Nzo.
      - Other Organisations/Individuals (includes - CHISA, Committee for Health in Southern Africa) (Box B8., Folder 6.3)
        - Correspondence/Reports (4 items), 1986-1990 (Box B8., Folder 6.3.1)
          Items include Declaration on Health in Southern Africa. Maputo, April 15 1990.
    - Department of International Affairs (Box B8., Folder 7)
      - Acting Head-- S. Molifi (Box B8., Folder 7.1)
        - Correspondence (32 items), 1983-1987
      - General (Box B8., Folder 7.2)
        - Correspondence (33 items), 1970-1991 (Box B8., Folder 7.2.1)
        - Reports (10 items), 1978, 1981-1986 (Box B8., Folder 5.7.2.2)
        - Statements (7 items), 1982-1988 (Box B8., Folder 7.2.4)
        - Statements/Other (1 item), 1989 (Box B8., Folder 7.2.4)
          High Commissioner of the Cooperative Republic of Guyana.
        - Miscellaneous (8 items) (Box B8., Folder 7.2.5)
      - ANC External Missions (Box B8., Folder 7.3)
        - Algeria Report (1 item), 1990 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.1)
        - Angola (10 items), 1985-1990 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.2)
          Correspondence--New Year compliments/relaying of a message from Flt-Lt Jerry Rawlings to Oliver Tambo on the occasion of the 77th Anniversary of the ANC.
        - Asia (2 items), undated, 1985 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.3)
          List; Correspondence--informing Oliver Tambo the Jawaharlal Nehru University wishes to confer the degree of Doctor of Laws Honoris Causa on him.
        - Australasia/Pacific (28 items), 1983-1989 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.4)
          - Correspondence/Reports (Box B8., Folder 7.3.4.1)
            - Report of the Australasian and Pacific Mission: Sydney, 1989 November
            - Briefing Notes. Visit to the ANC of the Australia n Minister for Foreign Affairs, Hon. Gareth Evans QC MP.
            - Prime Ministerial Statement on South Africa. House of Representatives, 1986 August 21
          - South Africa: Actions taken by the Australia n Government, 1983-1988 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.4.1)
          - Statements (Box B8., Folder 7.3.4.2)
            - Address by the Minister for Foreign Affairs and Trade, Senator Gareth Evans, to the ANC Regional Conference Against Apartheid For A Democratic South Africa, Sydney, 1989 September 15
            - Australian ANC Support Committee Annual Report (includes pamphlet), 1989
            - Minister for Foreign Affairs and Trade News Release
            - SAPSAN ( Special Assistance Program to South Africans and Namibians) Annual Report, 1987-1988
            - SAPSAN Annual Report, 1988-1989
            - APHEDA supported ANC Projects, 1986-1989
            - SA - New Zealand Government Position (statements)
          - Sticker--Act Now! Against Apartheid (Box B8., Folder 7.3.4.3)
          - Regional Conference Against Apartheid for a Democratic South Africa, Sydney, 1989 September 15-17 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.4.4)
            - Programme/Reports/Speeches/Communiqué
        - Botswana (2 items), 1984 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.5)
          - Correspondence
        - Brussels (5 items), 1990 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.6)
          - Correspondence/Reports
          - Outline of the functioning of the Brussels ANC Mission (first 6 months of 1990)
          - Visit of Comrade Nelson Mandela to the European Parliament and the European Economic Commission, 1990 June 12 - 14
        - Canada (13 items), 1970-1991 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.7)
          - Correspondence--Manitoba Anti-Apartheid Coalition for Majority Rule in Southern Africa
          - Report, 1982
            - Canadian Labour Congress Report: presented by Steve September (Winnipeg Unit)
        - Cuba (Box B8., Folder 7.3.8)
          - Reports/Correspondence (4 items), undated, 1988
            - Reports by the ANC Representative ( Raymond Nkuku) in Cuba to Oliver Tambo.
            - Financial Report ( Stanley Manana)
        - Denmark (1 item), 1988 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.9)
          - Correspondence
        - East Africa (See also Kenya Mission) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.10)
          - Correspondence (20 items), 1971-1989 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.10.1)
          - Reports (6 items), 1965, 1981, 1986, 1989 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.10.2)
            - Afro-Asian Economic Seminar, 1965 February
            - Temeke Incident (Memorandum/Statements), 1981
            - Meeting of the Chief Representative East Africa with Ambassador of Guinea Conakry
            - Brief Report on ANC Work in East Africa, 1988 November
            - Chief Representative’s Report ( Tanzania)
          - Miscellaneous (3 items) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.10.3)
            - Telegram to Winnie Dadoo/Coded Message
        - Egypt (3 items), 1975, 1988-1989 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.11)
          - Correspondence
        - Ethiopia (1 item), 1985 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.12)
        - India (1 item), 1971 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.13)
          - Correspondence
        - Italy (4 items), 1972, 1982, 1989 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.14)
          - Correspondence/Report
        - Kenya (Box B8., Folder 7.3.15)
          - Report-- Thami Sindelo, 1988 October 10
        - Madagascar (Box B8., Folder 7.3.16)
          - Reports/Correspondence (12 items), 1973, 1979, 1982 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.16.1)
            - Message sent by Didier Ratsiraka, President of the Democratic Republic of Madagascar to Dr. Kurt Waldheim, Secretary General of the UN, 1979 March
            - A plot against Ratsiraka: correspondent - Bolofo Rasoarahoma, 1982
            - Items relating to an incident in which members of the ANC Radio Unit were detained and consequently repatriated to Tanzania, 1982
          - Visits to Seychelles (Box B8., Folder 7.3.16.2)
            - Diplomatic Cards (3 items)
            - Reports
              - Pretoria Connection, 1981 December 21 - 1982 January 3
              - Report on visit to the Republic of Seychelles, 1982 January 29 - February 5
            - Press Cuttings--relating to South African mercenary attack, 1981 November
        - Mozambique (5 items), 1984-1987 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.17)
          - Correspondence/Reports
            - Reports on developments, 1984 September, 1985 January, 1986 July - August
            - Memorandum on the situation in Mozambique after the death of President Machel
        - Namibia (4 items), 1991 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.18)
        - Netherlands (Amsterdam Office, 2 items), 1989 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.19)
          - Correspondence
        - Nigeria (5 items), 1985-1989 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.20)
          - Correspondence/Report
        - Sweden (Nordic Countries, 8 items), 1982, 1988-1989 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.21)
          - Correspondence/Report
        - United Kingdom and Ireland (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22)
          - Correspondence (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.1)
            - 1962-1978 (46 items) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.1a)
              Correspondents include Mendi Msimang; Reg September.
            - 1985, 1989-1991 (25 items) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.1b)
              Includes memoranda; Correspondents include Mendi Msimang (Chief Representative)
          - Memoranda (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.2)
            - 1989 January - July (9 items) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.2a)
              - Memorandum on Sechaba: Some Thoughts on its Aims and Needs.
              - Book proposal on Robert McBride.
              - Draft Introduction by Brain Wrobel to the Report to the British Parliamentary Human Rights Group including the three responses by the ANC, the South African regime and Inkatha.
              - ANC/ IRA Allegations.
              - EEC and Sanctions.
            - 1989 August (10 items) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.2b)
              - Lausanne Colloquium ("The Mixed Economy of a Democratic South Africa"): Paper presented by Professor Lawrence Harris.
              - The Mandela Football Club.
              - Political Prisoners’ Committee Report.
            - 1989 November - December (17 items) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.2c)
              - Meeting between WUS ( UK) and this Mission.
              - Sechaba (A Festival of Cultural Resistance to Apartheid), Glasgow.
              - Allegations of torture by SWAPO.
              - Third World Prize Award for 1989.
              - Swiss Labour Assistance to ANC.
            - 1990 January (11 items) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.2d)
              - Southern African Coalition.
              - The Nelson Mandela National Reception Committee - Britain.
              - Notes of Meeting with Hungarian Ambassador and our office.
              - Memorandum on meeting at Foreign and Commonwealth Office.
            - 1990 February - April (9 items) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.2e)
              - A TOAISEAGH (Prime Minister) Charles Haughey invitation to Comrade Nelson Mandela.
              - Projected visit to the United Kingdom by the Deputy President, Comrade Nelson Mandela.
          - Press Statements (2 items), 1989, 1991 (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.3)
          - Miscellaneous (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.4)
            - ANC Catalogue (clothing; posters; accessories and other ANC paraphernalia)
          - Regional Preparatory Committee (RPC) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.5)
            - Correspondence/Agenda/Questionnaire (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.5a)
            - Publication (Box B8., Folder 7.3.22.5b)
        - Union of Soviet Socialist Republic ( USSR) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.23)
          - Correspondence (5 items), 1988-1990
            Includes a New Year’s message to Oliver Tambo.
        - United States of America ( USA) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.24)
          - Correspondence (15 items), 1973, 1983, 1988-1991
            Includes correspondence between Dumi Matabane and Oliver Tambo).
        - Report/Memorandum (1 item), 1988
          - State of Organisation
        - Zambia (Box B8., Folder 7.3.25)
          - Correspondence (Box B8., Folder 7.3.25.1)
            - undated, 1966-1969 (19 items) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.25.1a)
              Correspondents include T. T. Nkobi (Chief Representative).
            - 1970 (15 items) (Box B8., Folder 7.3.25.1b)
              Correspondents include: T. T. Nkobi (Chief Representative).